(Howard:)And whistles.
(Bernadette:)At any point did it dawn on you to talk
to me about spending this kind of money?
(Howard:)It's kind of dawning on me now.
(Bernadette:)I don't believe you.
(Bernadette:)Howie, we can't afford to waste money
on junk like this.
(Howard:)What are you talking about?
We make plenty of money.
(Bernadette:)I make plenty of money.
You make peanuts.
Well, yes, but we're married now.
(Howard:)That means when you get sick,
I take care of you.
(Howard:)And when you make a bunch of money...
(Howard:)...I get to buy stuff.
(Howard:)Sorry if you don't like it,
but that's how love works.
(Bernadette:)No. Here's how love works.
You're gonna return the machine...
...or you could print out a working set
of lady parts and sleep with those.
(Bernadette:)Oh, my God.
Are you actually thinking about it?
(Penny:)I don't understand.
Why didn't you just tell Kripke the truth?